<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gates 2k16</string>
    <string-array name="list1">
        <item>Event 1</item>
        <item>Event 2</item>
        <item>Event 3</item>
        <item>Event 4</item>
        <item>Event 5</item>
        <item>Event 6</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="openDrawer">Drawer Open</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">Drawer Close</string>
    <string name="gtbit">
        <![CDATA[
                <p>
                    <h1 style="color:#FFFFFF;">
                        Introduction
                    </h1>
                   <br/>
                   <h3>
                        What is Bash?
                   </h3>
                </p>
                <p>
                    \t<b>Bash</b> is a command processor that typically runs in a text window
                    where the user types commands that cause actions. Bash can also read
                    commands from a file, called a <b>script</b>. Like all Unix shells,
                    it supports <i>filename globbing (wildcard matching), piping,
                     command substitution, variables and control structures
                    for condition-testing and iteration</i>. The keywords, syntax and other basic
                    features of the language were all copied from sh. Other features, e.g.,
                    history, were copied from csh and ksh. Bash is a <b>POSIX</b>(Portable Operating System Interface)
                     shell, but with a number of extensions.
                </p>
                <p>
                    \t<b>Bash</b> was written for the <b>GNU Project</b> by <i>Brian Fox</i>.
                    It is called <b><u>Bourne again shell</u></b> for many reasons, the first being that
                    it is the open-source version of the <i>Bourne shell</i> and the second as a pun
                    on the concept of being born again. Its acronym is also a description of what
                    the project did, which was to bash together sh, csh and ksh features.
                </p>
                <p>
                    \tEssentially, <b>Bash</b> allows users of Unix-like systems to control the innermost
                    components of the operating system using text-based commands. Anything you can run
                    normally on the command line can be put into a script and it will do exactly the same
                    thing. Similarly, anything you can put into a script can also be run normally on the
                    command line and it will do exactly the same thing.
                </p>
                    \t<b>Bash</b> has a number of extensions and runs on Unix-like operating systems like
                    Linux and Mac OS X. It was ported to Windows through the Subsystem for UNIX-based
                    Applications (SUA) and by POSIX emulation using Cygwin or MSYS. It can even be used in MS-DOS.
                </p>
                <br/>
                <p>
                   <h3>
                        Why learn Bash?
                   </h3>
                </p>
                <p>
                    \tBash is better than any standard programming language when it comes to web app deployment,
                    system administration, automated backups and data crunching. And Bash is better when you want
                    to run a lot of programs in series. Bash is good for day to day system administration. If you\'re
                    going to learn how to use a UNIX shell, Bash is probably the best choice.
                </p>
            ]]>
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
